Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5786
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Settled Cases (1979-1983). (Box 11)
  - Stop & Shop & UFCW #1445 AAA/ Boston 1130-1153-80, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - ACME Markets/ Local 169 1430-0229-81 4/28/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - A&P & Local 10- A AAA/HART #1230-0327-80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Air Force Arbitration Program Crystal City VA June 2-8, 82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - AMCHEM Prod. & Warehouse Employees/ 1430-2103-80J 9/4/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Boulder Valley School District Mediation Colorado Nov. 15-17 '82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - NAA: Canadian Region Meeting Nov. 5-6 1982 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Commnwealth of Massachusetts - MNA 4/30/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Commnwealth of Massachusetts/ SEIU, Welfare 6/25, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Connecticut Light & Power - IBEW, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - FAA/ PATCO (3 cases) NY Aug. 5&6 1981 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union discharge Los Angeles 7/14/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Greyhound Lines/ Amalgamated Transit Union Los Angeles Jan. 6&7 1982, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union termination Los Angeles Spet. 16' 81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union Grievance. Cleveland, OH Oct. 23, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Greyhound/Amalgamated Transit Union grievance. Syracuse NY 5/1/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union Case Syracuse, NY 5/19/82, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union Discharge New York City 21 April, 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union Discharge San Francisco Dec. 14 '82, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - ITT Grinnell/ Local 376 (80-153) Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Milford Board Of Education/CEA (11/18/82) 12 39 0261 82 Milford, CT., 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - University of Minnesota 1982 Arbitration conf. Nov. 30- Dec.1 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - NAA- Mohonk Mt. House Nov. 11-13 ' 81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Nabisco Confections 1130-0347-82 AAA Boston 5/24/82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Philadelphia NAA 3/17/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - City of Philadelphia & APTA 1430 0900 79 J 9/17+18, 10/1/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - City of Philadelphia 1430-0065-81 AAA- Phila. 9/14/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Philadelhia School District/ Teachers 1439-1814-82, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Quincy School Committee/ QEA PS 4-83 Fact Finding Mediation, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Rock of Ages/ Steelworkers Barre, Vt., 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Salem, N.H. School Board. Meditation 1/28/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Sanborn NH Regional School District & Education Association Feb. 2&3 '81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - St. Louis University Seminar 4/24/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - SPIDR Conference Philadelphia June 19 1981 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Texas International Airport / ALPA Grievance. Houston, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - TWA/ ALPA Grievance New York City 2/2/82, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - TWA/ ALPA Case NYC June 28,29,30 ' 82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - USPS & APWU NYC Discharge 3/10/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - USPS - NALC Grievance. Bberthiaume 2/11 +12/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - USPS- APWU Discharge New York City 5/28/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - USPS N8N-IE-D-14078 Discharge. Boston 9/25/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - USPS N8N-IE-D-18N2 Discharge Boston 9/23/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - USPS/NALC (2 cases) Boston 5/7/82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - USPS/APWU Grievance. Boston, MA 6/18/82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - USPS/APWU (3 Cases) Hartford May14, 1982, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - USPS/APWU New Haven, CT 8/05/82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - USPS/ APWU Grievances (3) Worcester, MA Dec.10 ' 82, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Union Butterfield/ IAMAW 1130 1601-81, Newport, VT 10/19/81 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - United Airline/ AFA Hutchens Chicago SF 6-81 6/23/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - United Airlines grievance. Chicago. Il 6/24/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - United Airlines/ AFA Grievance. Chicago MEC-14-80 6/22/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Union Butterfield/ IAMAW 1130-1601-81, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - S.D. Warren Co. & UPIU, Local 1069, 1130-1949-80 6/16/81, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Adams County School 11/26/84 District Col. + 11/30/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Aluminum Processing/ IBEW 1130-1905-83 1/9/84 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Beefsteak Charlie's/ 11/27/84 Local 26 Boston, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Bonwit Tellers 10/29/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Boston Edison/ Clerical Workers 1130-2173-83, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Boston Archdiocese Teachers Association 11/14/84 Archdiocesan High School Of Boston, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Cleveland Electric Illuminating Co/ UWUA 53 30 0068 84 8/1/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Connecticut Yankee Greyhound Racing 12 30 0320 83 1/18/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Filene's/Local 1445 UFCW 1130-1759-83 1/12/84, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Frontier Air/ AFA 11/19/84 9:00 AM Denver (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Greyhound/ Local 1205 Boston 9/26/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Hershey Foods Corp./ Local 464 ' 84 Hershey, PA, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Internal Revenue Service Prog. March 28, 1984 Wash. D.C. (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - ITT Grinnell/Local 376 Lancaster, PA 6/5/84 1984 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Univ. of Minnesota 11/13/84 Conference, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Mobil Oil/ Ind Oil Wrks 12/10/84 Philadelphia, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Northwest Orient/ IBT 9/20&21/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Northwest Airlines/ BRAC Minn,- St. Paul Jan. 31, Feb.1 84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Phila. S.D./ American Federatin Of Teachers 1439-0581-83Q Jan. 10 1984, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Superior Tube Company/ USWA AAA Philadelphia (0145-84) 1984 9/5/1984 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Thompson Education Association 12/6/84 Thompson School District. Mediation Col, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Triangle Container Corp United Paperworkers Local 286, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - ITT Grinnell/ Local 376 #84-11, 9/7/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - USPS/ APWU 7/3/84 Albany, N.Y., 1984 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - USPS/AWU Union, NJ Cancellation 5/31/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - USPS/NAC NYC Cancellation 5/11/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - USPS/APWU New York City 4/27/84, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - USPS/ NALC Enfield, CT 4/13/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - USPS/APWU Stamford, Ct 9/14/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - USPS/ NALC NYC 03/02/84, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - USPS/ APWU 12/5/84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - WGBH/NABET 10:00, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Wilbur Chocolate/ Local 464 1430 0073 84W Lancaster, Pa, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Yale University/ Local 35 Cancellation of hearings. 3/29+4/2, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - USPS/APWU 12/4/84 Jersey City NJ, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - AAA Great Gorge Summer Workshop- July 27-28, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - AAA Arbitration Workshop, Hyannis July 27-29, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Beefsteak Charlies/ Local 26 Boston, Ma 1983 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Colonnade Hotel/ Local 261130-1463-83 12/6/83, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Commonwealth Of Massachusetts (DMH)/ AFSCME Grievance. #82-530 6/15/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Commonwealth Of Massachusetts/ Alliance Dept. Mental Health 6/8/1983 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Commonwealth Of Massachusetts/ MNA Laoyff of DPH RNs 10/4/83, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Commonwealth Of Massachusetts/ NMA Demotion 10/11/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Commonwealth Of Massachusetts/ MNA suspension. 10/17/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Connecticut Union Of Telephone Workers Seminar at Yale Conn. 4/18/83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union Grievance. Evansville, Ind. April 20, '83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union Discharge San Francisco 5/18, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Harvard University/ Local 26 1130-1083-83 Nov. 3 ' 83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Harvard University/Local 26 1130-104-83 10/20/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - HERCO/ Local 464 Storeroom & Utility Jobs 5/4/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Lowell Sun / Local 32 News. Guild 1130-0044-83 Sept. 13, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Massachusetts Teachers' Association/ Field Services Organization 2/28/83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Massachusetts Transit Administration/ Amalgamated Transit Union 1430 1300 83R Baltimore 15/5/83, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - N.E. Environmental Mediation May 5, 1983/ Radcliffe College (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Usen Corp./Local 15 Gloucester, MA Nov. ' 83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Pheasant Run Conference, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Philadelphia School District/ American Federation of Teachers. 1439-0847-82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Public Service Elec. & Gas AAA NY (1488-82) May 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Rock of Ages Corp./Local 4 Suspension For Absenteeism / / 83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Ritz Carlton Hotel/ Local 26 1130-0704-83 10/3/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Smithfield School Committee/ NEA 1139-0259-83, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Uniroyal/ URW 1983 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - United Airlines/AFA Chicago, Il July2, ' 83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Western Pennsylvania Water Co. / UWUA Local 537. (5530-0289-82) ' 83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Wyman Gordon Co./ Steelworkers Auburn, MA 9/12/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - USPS/APWU Bronx Cases New York City 1/21/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - USPS/APWU 2/4/83 A/P, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - USPS/APWU Grievance. Pitsfield. MA 3/04/83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - USPS/APWU New Haven, Ct July 21, ' 83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - USPS/ APWU New Haven, CT /10/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - USPS/APWU Class Action Cases Albany, NY 6/2/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - USPS/APWU Class Action Cases Albany, NY 4/29/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - USPS/APWU Class Action Cases Albany, NY 4/28/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - USPS/NALC Grievance. Providence, R.I. Spet. 16. ' 83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - USPS/APWU Springfield, MA 6/17/83 (3W'D), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - USPS/ APWU Grievance. Lawrence, MA Sept. 23, ' 83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - USPS/APWU (6 cases) Manchester, NH 5/20/93, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - USPS 4 case Harford, CT NALC 5/13/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - USPS/ APWU (3 Cases) Springfield, MA 4/8/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - USPS/ Mailhandlers Springfield, MA 12/22/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - USPS/ NALC Class Action Cases Albany, New York 12/16/83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - USPS/APWU 12/14/83 Contract Cases NJ Jersey City, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - USPS/NALC Contract Cases NH Portsmouth, NH 12/19/83 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - USPS/NALC Contract Cases NH Portsmouth, NH 12/19/83 (Box 11, Folder 189)